Let's talk about how we human characterize and describe earthquakes.
让我们来讨论一下人类是如何表示和描述地震的
Earthquakes occur everyday, all over the world.
从全世界范围来看 每天都有地震发生
The result of the energy being released through seismic activity,
这可能是由于地震活动释放的能量
which can be caused by tectonic plate movement, volcanic activity, or
也可能是由地壳运动、火山活动造成的
even advanced like meteor impact or nuclear weapon that nation.
甚至一些更高端的原因 像是陨石撞击或者核武器引爆
Earthquakes can be described in terms of their magnitude,
地震可以通过一些术语来描述 如震级
epicenter, depth, date, and so on.
震中、震源深度、时间等等
We might want to display some of these properties in our app.
我们想要在我们的应用中显示其中的某些属性
All right, taking a quick glance around the USGS homepage.
那么现在让我们快速浏览一下　USGS　主页
It looks like a lot of the information that we want is here.
这里看起来有很多我们想要获取的信息
Let's check out an earthquake to see what we got.
让我们点击一则地震新闻 看看我们将能够得到什么
This looks good.
看起来还不错
We've got maps, we've got time.
我们能够看到地图和发生的时间
You've got near by places, descriptions of location.
还有地震位置以及周边的情况
Magnitude up here, looking good.
这里显示了震级 看起来还不错
All right, let's back up and see if we can find any developer oriented
那么现在让我们返回上一个页面 看看是否能发现
information that we can work with.
一些我们可以使用的开发者信息
All right, if I scroll down here's a link for real time feeds and
好的 我们向下滑动页面 我看到了一个实时反馈和通知的
notifications.
链接
Let's see what we get in here.
让我们点击看看
Looks like there's a lot of useful ways to consume the USGS earthquake
这里好像提供了很多方式 可以购买 USGS
data here.
地震信息
ATOM syndication is used for feed readers,
ATOM Syndication 用于实时反馈
this earthquake notification service can send you an email or
而 Earthquake Notification Service 在地震发生时
cellphone alert when earthquake's happen.
能够给你发送邮件 或者打警报电话
Use Google Earth KML to visualize earthquakes around the globe right
使用 Google Earth KML 能够在 Google 地图范围内
within Google Earth.
预测地震
We got access to Tweeter, Spreadsheet Format and QuakeML.
访问 Tweeter 或者 Spreadsheet Format 和 QuakeML
Let's take a look at the Spreadsheet Format for a minute.
让我们花一分钟看看 Spreadsheet Format
So looks like this page has a good description of the Spreadsheet Format
Spreadsheet Format 中有对地震的详细描述
including the types of field that we would build access.
甚至包括我们想要建立访问的字段类型
And in fact, there's a little screenshot here, that shows what it would look
哦 事实上 这里有一些截图 显示了如果你把这些内容
like if you imported this into Excel or Google Sheets.
导入 Excel 或 Google Sheets 其将如何显示
And you can see right at the top, we got headings for
我们从左到右看一下第一行
Time, Latitude,Longitude, Debt, and Mag for magnitude.
时间、纬度、经度以及震级
And we can see what the data format looks like this was like a timestamp,
我们可以看到这些数据格式是如何写的 如 时间戳
latitude and longitude or numbers and depth is a number,
经度和纬度 或者震源的深度
magnitude is a number so good.
震级的大小
We have some information to work with here.
这里有很多有用的信息
It looks like the USGS earthquake data is structured in a way that we
看起来 USGS 地震数据的结构对我们的应用开发
might find useful for our app.
很有帮助